well credit Swiss is positive on the
insurance sector first up they've
initiated coverage on ICICI Lombard what
they suggest is the key trigger is going
to be motor insurance FY 2324 they
believe holds the key for motor
insurance and growth will start kicking
in in these particular years what
they've done is they've said that uh the
stock has derated from its longterm mean
of 40 times 24 month forward to 25 times
24 month forward So currently they are
valuing it at 32 times 24 months forward
and ascribing it a valuation of 1,400
rupees a share the stock gain nearly 5%
yesterday uh so a positive there what
they are seeing is that there is a
delayed Roe recovery uh for the counter
which is what is uh pushing a discount
uh on the multiple of the stock and they
believe that execution on the growth as
well as the retail Health franchise will
help Drive the stock up and rate the
stock as well on another counter they're
talking about credit uh credit Swiss is
also talking about star Health what they
believe is that health insurance uh
which has been under pressure uh largely
due to the insurance regulator looking
at life insurance to enter the health
insurance space is what is putting
pressure on the stock they've again
initiated and outperform with a Target
price of 600 rupees a share they're
expecting growth uh to outperform the
industry where star health is concerned
they're expecting an earnings bounce
back and they're expecting the ratios
claims ratios to start improving as
covid starts fading what they are seeing
is premium growth will be led by
continued agent Network expansion so
they are seeing a few positives they're
saying that the negatives are already
built into the stock and this is uh an
currently an outperform as per credit
Swiss